What was the question again?
So the question is, like, a positive experience
we've had with AI, where it's helped enhance
our productivity learning specifically in the
lab.
Cool.
So, I can go first. Yeah, I don't know how many.
I would say one of the best ways was,
with the experimentations that we've been running
on the tower, there's a lot that we didn't understand
at first that we were kind of just doing to get
started,
and I helped get started on that.
came a point where I was like, oh,
I don't really know what's going on with it.
So instead of just asking it what to do next,
what we did was we asked, like, how does this
work? What are you doing with this?
Give us some source papers and stuff is basically
the thing that I sent to it.
And it provided back a lot of stuff that obviously
I had to go through in like source check and
stuff.
But the papers and stuff that it provided were
pretty good because I could go and find these
papers and see how they relate.
Are they good?
And those provided good information for, like,
actually learning what was going on and helped
enhance it in that way.
There's a lot of ways it's enhanced productivity
with being able to analyze data quickly and stuff
with things we already know what it's doing.
But, yeah.
Nice, nice, nice. This one's pretty good stuff.
For me,
you know, haven't done anything in this lab quite
yet.
So not much, but I guess an experience in a
different lab. that I've done.
We,
I had to custom make threads because we had
a female part, but we
had to make a new male part without ordering
it online. So I had to learn how to custom make
the threads. It taught me how to make the threads,
which was pretty good, although it made the diameter
of the circle too big. So I
had to make small adjustments, like making it
the right size.
But it taught me how to make the teeth.
pretty well.
That's pretty good. It's funny how bad AI's spatial
reasoning is.
Like, it really has no concept of, like, 3D space
at all. I mean, it makes sense because it's just
an algorithm.
But,
yeah. Yeah, like, the way you have it, sure,
yes, it would fit,
but it wouldn't thread. It wouldn't twist.
Yeah, the thrust. Yeah, I could just, you know,
it's in. It's like the funny thing is, like,
the auger design that they've been doing.
I don't know how much of it you've seen, but
it's for, like, a power dispenser,
and they had AI doing all of the generative CAD
for it.
And at the beginning, it was really funny because
there'd be all these things, like, great ideas,
and there'd be, like, parts where just, like,
it couldn't move because the parts interfered
so much with each other.
Well, like, the connector wasn't attached to
the body or things like that.
Like, that AI just doesn't realize.
But,
yeah, I think teaching as, like, that is a really
good, good thing. Anyway, anything else you want
to add? Nope.
Fiss out.